Harrison S. Morris Papers, 1784-1970 (bulk 1895-1935 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 9: Papers of Others, 1884-1957; 135.0 boxes
  - Subseries 9A: Family, 1882-1957; more than 18 boxes
    - Catherine Morris Wright, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
      - Harrison Smith Memorial Exhibition, dates not examined; 4.0 folders
        - Miscellaneous Material, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        - Printed Matter, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - Jane Walters Morris, 1891-1950; 3.0 boxes
      - Correspondence, 1891-1945; 8.0 folders (Folder 1-8)
      - Miscellaneous Cards, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1943-1950; 1.0 item (Folder 1-5)
      - Christmas Cards, 1948-1950; 1.0 item (Folder 6-8)
      - Address and Telephone Books, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Baptismal and Confirmation Certificates, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Bank Books--Checking, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Bills and Receipts, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Document--Wills (Copies), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Financial Record Books, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous Jottings, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Prints Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - United States Income Tax Return, 1948; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Matilda Morris, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
    - Morris Harris Families, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
      - Aunt Em, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Aunt Till, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Cagill, Charles B., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Dovey, Adelaide Hays (Aunt Add), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Dovey, Nan, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Grandmother, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Harris Family--Salem, New Jersey, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Harris, Katherine, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Harris, Matilde, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - Harris, Shepherd, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - Harris, Tach and Ella, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - Hewett, Jane (Mrs. Clarence Hewett), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - Hockley, Marran S. (Stretch), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - Levensetter, [Jane], dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - Morris Family, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - Morris, George Washington, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - Morris, Mrs. George Washington, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - Morris, Mathilda--Condolence Letters, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - Ohl, Mabel (Mrs. Frederick W.), dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Stretch, Johnathan "Jack", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Stretch, Marshall & Josephine, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Stretch, May S., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Tasker, Lee, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Tasker, Mary H., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Genealogy--Harrison Smith Morris, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Harris Family History, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Morris, George Washington, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9-10)
        diary, financial records, recipe books for medicines, miscellaneous material
    - Holiday Greeting Cards--Family Memorabilia, dates not examined; 10.0 folders
      - Anniversary, Holiday Cards, Memorabilia, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Birthdays--prior to 80th, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - 80th Birthday, dates not examined; 5.0 folders
        - Poems, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        - Thank You Letters, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        - Cards, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
        - Letters and Telegrams, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
        - Plaque--Art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Birthdays--post 80th, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Painting--John Morris, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - Valentines, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
        From Anna Wharton Morris, Catherine Morris Wright, Sydney Wright, Anna Wright, Harrison Wright, Elicott Wright, Redwood Wright
  - Subseries 9B: Aix Les Bains, 1914-1916; 6.0 folders
    Consists of works by Aix Les Bains regarding the Packard Automobile.
    - General, 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - Re: Packard Automobile, 1915-1916; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc American Association, 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - Financial Matter, 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
    - Printed Matter & Miscellaneous Material, 1914; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
  - Subseries 9C: American Philosophical Society, 1901 July 30-1946; 3.0 boxes
    Consists of works by the American Philosophical Society, such as "The Art Called Modern" and "The Revolt Against Taste."
    - Papers, 1932 April-1942 April; 6.0 folders
      - "The Art Called Modern", 1932 April 1; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Illusions", 1937 April; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Invention & Intervention", 1942 April; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "One of the Wits of the Franklin Inn...", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "The Revolt Against Taste", 1935 April 18; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "Some Reflections on Picasso Exhibit at the Chicago Art Institute", 1940 April; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1903-1946; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - Invitations, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
    - Loose Pages, 1920 February-1933 March 23; portion of 1 box
      - "The Revolt Against Taste", dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Report of the Committee on Finance, 1932 December 30; 1.0 item
      - Report of the Committee on Finance, 1933 March 23; 1.0 item
      - Hall of the American Philosophical Society, 1920 February; 1.0 item
    - Bound Works, 1901 July 30-1946 July 26; 2.0 boxes (1 partial)
      - Mankind Advancing American Philosophical Society, 1929; 1.0 item
      - The List of the American Philosophical Society, 1926 January; 1.0 item
      - The List of the American Philosophical Society, 1931 July; 1.0 item
      - The American Philosophical Society Charter Laws and Rules of Order, 1921 December; 1.0 item
      - Franklin's Bagatelles (reprint), 1901 July 30; 1.0 item
      - The "Franklin Papers" in The American Philosophical Society "Illusions" by Morris (reprint), 1937; 1.0 item
      - Nominations for Membership, 1944; 1.0 item
      - Nominations for Membership, 1941; 1.0 item
      - Nominations for Membership, 1915; 1.0 item
      - Nominations for Membership, 1943; 1.0 item
      - Report of the Committee on Library, 1938; 1.0 item
      - Report of the Committee on Finance, 1938; 1.0 item
      - Servants of Mankind (American Philosophical Society), 1930; 1.0 item
      - Intellectual Stock-Taking (American Philosophical Society), 1929; 1.0 item
      - Report of the Committee on Research, 1938; 1.0 item
      - Year-Book, 1943; 1.0 item
      - Year-Book, 1942; 1.0 item
      - Year-Book, 1940; 1.0 item
      - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1916; 1.0 item
      - Report on the Committee on Research, 1940; 1.0 item
      - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1916 August-September; 1.0 item
      - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1946 July 26; 1.0 item
      - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1945 April 30; 1.0 item
      - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1945 October 11; 1.0 item
      - Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, 1945 December 10; 1.0 item
      - Year-Book, 1941; 1.0 item
      - Year-Book, 1945; 1.0 item
    - Membership Nominations, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - Announcements of Meetings, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
    - Laws, 1934; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - Officers, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - Printed Matter, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
    - Reports, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
  - Subseries 9D: Art Association of Newport, 1909-1948; 12.0 boxes
    Consists of works by the Art Association of Newport, such as "Taste" and "American Art of Today."
    - Works, 1917 August 27-1928 April; 6.0 folders
      - "American Art of Today", 1928 April; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "American Painting and Painters" (speech), 1927 September 10; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - "Anecdote of Locomotive and Corner Grocery", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - "Art in Newport", 1917 September 12; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "Taste", 1918 April; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - "The Unexpected Always Happens...", 1917 August 27; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1909-1948; 6.0 boxes (1 partial)
      - A-Z, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7-11)
      - Walter Coles Cabell, 1916-1932; 1.0 item (Folder 1-5)
      - Maud Howe Elliot, 1909-1926; 1.0 item (Folder 1-3)
      - Maude Howe Elliot and Walter Coles Cabell, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Maude Howe Elliot, 1916-1941; 1.0 item (Folder 1-2)
      - Grand Central Galleries, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Ruth Thomas, 1922-1941; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Edith T. Pearce, 1919-1948; 1.0 item (Folder 1-2)
      - Margaret H. Laird, 1932-1946; 1.0 item (Folder 3-4)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, dates not examined; 7.0 folders
        - Pauline Adderson, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
        - River Case "Swanhurst", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
        - Swanhurst, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        - Gilbert Stuart Memorial, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        - Peyton Hazard, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
        - Marion King, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
        - Helena Sturvesant, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - Annual Art Exhibitions, 1918-1941; 2.0 boxes
      - Exhibit, 1938; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Exhibit, 1937; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Exhibit, 1936; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Show, 1935; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Show, 1934; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Show, 1933; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Show, 1919; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Show, 1918; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Exhibit, 1941; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Exhibit, 1940; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Exhibit, 1939; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - Documents, dates not examined; more than 4 folders
      - Bylaws, Agreements, etc., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Financial Records--Aquidneck National Bank, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Financial Records--General, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3-6)
      - Rhode Island Hospital Frost Company, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
    - Photographs, School Drawings, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - Minutes of Meetings, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3-4)
    - Miscellaneous Material, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1-4)
    - Printed Material, 1910 July-1940 October; 1.0 box
      - The Bylaws of the Art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Fifth Morris Memorial Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - School of the Art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Paintings by R. H. Ives Cammell, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Loan Exhibition of Paintings & Drawings by Charles Morris Young, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Fifty Famous Painters (exhibition catalogue), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue of Paintings Relating to Colonial Newport by Helena [Storveuant], dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting & Sculpture, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue of the Thirty-Eighth Annual Water Color and Print Exhibition, undated; 1.0 item
        Published by the Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts
      - New Hope Art Associates Gallery, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Second National Exhibition of the Society for Sanity in Art, Inc., dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport: Third Annual Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport: Sixth Annual Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (appeal), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport Twenty Second Annual Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1934 January; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1933 April; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1932 April; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1932 October; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1931 October; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1930 October; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1930 April; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1930 April; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1917 April; 1.0 item
      - Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society, 1913 July; 1.0 item
      - Newport Historical Society (leaflet), 1926 September 18; 1.0 item
      - "The Old House at 17 Broadway" (fragment) by Maud Lyman Stevens, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - A Decade of Newport (Bulletin of the Newport Historical Society), 1925 April; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue: The Art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Thirty-Third Annual Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Art and Progress: "American Artists in Rome" by Maude Howe, 1910 July; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Small Paintings by Moses Soyer (Macbeth Gallery), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by members of the art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - An Exhibition of Water Colors, Pastels, Drawings, Paints, and Sculpture (The Art Association of Newport), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport--Second Annual Exhibition, 1913; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport--Sixty Annual Exhibition, 1927; 1.0 item
      - National Academy (115th Annual Exhibition), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue of the One Hundred and Thirty-Sixth Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture, undated; 1.0 item
        Published by the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts.
      - Pictures on Exhibit, 1940 October; 1.0 item
      - The Fellowship of the Pennsylvania Academy of The Fine Arts--Annual Exhibition of Oil Paintings and Sculpture, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Paintings by Louis Kronberg, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Invitation Catalogue--Recent Paintings by Louis Kronberg, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Twenty Second Annual Exhibition of the Allied Artists of America, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Paintings by Gillerd Beal (Kraushaar Galleries), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Art Portfolio (Homer Martin) MacBeth Gallery, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue of Paintings relating to Colonial Newport (Art Association of Newport), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue of the Art Association of Newport Thirtieth Annual Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Birds and Flowers and Spring (Paintings by Jessie Arms Botke) Grand Central Art Galleries, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - An Exhibition of Recent Portraits by Members of the Guild of Barton Artists, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Exhibition of Paintings and Photographs by Adrian Siegel (Philadelphia Art Alliance), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Paintings by Louis Kronberg (Guild of Boston Artists), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Newport Social Index, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (Report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (Report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (Report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Seventeenth Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Art Paintings, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - National Academy (114th Annual Exhibition), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue: The Art Association of Newport, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - The Art Association of Newport (report), dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Catalogue: The Art Association of Newport--Twenty-Seventh Annual Exhibition, dates not examined; 1.0 item
      - Memorial Exhibition of Paintings by Lilla Cabot Perry, dates not examined; 1.0 item
  - Subseries 9E: Browning Society, 1894; 6.0 folders
    Consists of essays, correspondence, and information on meetings of the Browning Society.
    - Essays, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - "Browning Versus Browning", dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - General Meetings, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Notes, 1894; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Printed Matter, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
  - Subseries 9F: Committee of Ten, dates not examined; more than 4 folders
    Consists of radio announcements and correspondence of the Committee of Ten.
    - Radio Announcements, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 1-2)
    - Legislative Program, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Printed Matter, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
  - Subseries 9G: John Stevens Durham, 1889-1920; more than 3 folders
    Consists of correspondence and documents of John Stevens Durham.
    - Correspondence, 1889-1920; 3.0 folders (Folder 1-3)
    - Documents, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Printed Matter, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
  - Subseries 9H: Europe Travel, 1902-1906; more than 2 folders
    Consists of information regarding travel in Europe, 1902-1906.
    - England, 1906; 4.0 folders (Folder 1-4)
    - European Trip, 1902; 3.0 folders (Folder 5-7)
  - Subseries 9I: Franklin Inn Club, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
    Consists of correspondence regarding the Candidates for Admission to the Franklin Inn Club.
    - Correspondence re: Candidates for Admission, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Printed Material, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Material, dates not examined; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Announcements, dates not examined; 2.0 folders (Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries 9J: Hall of Fame, 1920-1946; 3.0 boxes
    Consists largely of information regarding nominees to the Hall of Fame, including Susan B. Anthony, Dorothea Dix, James Monroe, Thomas Paine, Elizabeth Cady Stanton, Walt Whitman, and Henry David Thoreau.
    Nominees arranged alphabetically.
    - Nominees, dates not examined; 2.0 boxes
      - Susan B. Anthony, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Henry Barnard, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Clara Barton, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - William Beaumont, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - George Rogers Clark, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - George Fisk Comfort, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - Dorothea Dix, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Mary Mapes Dodge, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Mary Baker Eddy, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - John Fitch, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - Stephen Collins Foster, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - Henry George, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - J. Willard Gibbs, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - Stephen Girard, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - John Hanson, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - Charles Goodyear, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - Townsend Harris, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - Clinton N. Hunt, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - Rafael Joselly, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - Sidney Lanier, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - Matthew Fontaine Maury, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      - Edward MacDowell, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      - Cyrus Hall McCormack, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - Robert McCormack, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Nominees, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      - James Monroe, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      - Lucretia Mott, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      - Simon Newcomb, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      - James Oglethorpe, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      - Thomas Paine, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      - William Penn, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      - Oliver Hazard Perry, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      - Mead Powell, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 14)
      - Howard Pyle, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      - Sara [?], dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 16)
      - Christopher Catham Sholes, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 17)
      - Elizabeth Cady Stanton, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - Zachary Taylor, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 19)
      - Sylvanus Thayer, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      - Theodore Thomas, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 21)
      - Henry David Thoreau, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
      - Joseph Word, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 23)
      - Walt Whitman, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 24)
      - Horace Wells, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
      - George Westinghouse, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1920-1946; 1.0 item (Folder 1-2)
    - Printed Matter: Handbooks, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
    - Printed Matter: Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
  - Subseries 9K: John McClure Hamilton & George Hall Hamilton, 1894-1940; more than 3 folders
    Consists largely of correspondence of John McClure Hamilton.
    - Hamilton, J.: Manuscript, 1921; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      "The Artist's Hymn," TMs, 1921
    - Hamilton, J.: Correspondence, 1894-1940; 1.0 item (Folder 2-4)
    - Hamilton, G., dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
  - Subseries 9L: International Exposition of Art, 1909-1915; more than 12 boxes
    Consists of information and works regarding the International Exposition of Art in Venice, 1909, and Rome, 1911.
    - Venice, 1909; 1.0 box
    - Rome, 1911; more than 11 boxes
      - "American Art at Rome", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      - "Art and Artifice in Italy", dates not examined; 1.0 item (Folder 2)